badcock.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy | Badcock &more

#### Privacy Policy

At Badcock, we take your privacy seriously, and we want you to know how we collect, use, share and protect information about you. By interacting with Badcock, you consent to our use of information that is collected or submitted as described in this privacy policy. We may change or add to this privacy policy, so we encourage you to review it periodically. 

This Privacy Policy tells you:

  * What information we collect
  * How we use that information
  * How we may share that information
  * How we protect your information
  * How we protect your information
  * Your choices regarding your personal information
  * How do you access and update your information

Information We Collect

**Information You Give Us**

Information You Give Us We receive and may store any information you enter on our website or give to us in our stores. For example, we collect information from you when you place an order, create an account, call us with a question, create a wish list or use any of our services. 

The information we collect from you includes things like:

  * Your name
  * Your mailing address
  * Your e-mail address
  * Your phone (or mobile) number
  * Your credit card number and other payment information
  * Your driver's license number
  * Credit application information, such as your Social Security number 
  * Demographic and lifestyle information, such as age, personal interests and product preferences 
  * send unsolicited or unauthorized email on behalf of Badcock, including promotions and/or advertising of products or services; 

**Information from Other Sources**

We may also receive information about you from other sources, including third parties that help us update, expand and analyze our records and identify new customers. 

We collect data that's publicly available. For example, information you submit in a public forum (e.g. a blog, chat room, or social network) can be read, collected, or used by us and others, and could be used to personalize your experience. You are responsible for the information you choose to submit in these instances. 

We may also obtain information provided by a third party. For instance, we obtain information from companies that can enhance our existing customer information to improve the accuracy and add to the information we have about our customers (for example, adding address information). This improves our ability to contact you and increases the relevance of our marketing by providing better product recommendations or special offers that may interest you. 

**Automated Information Collection**

We collect information related to your interactions with our website and apps to create a superior, personalized shopping experience, whether you are online or in our stores. This information includes your IP address, browsing behavior while on our site, browser and device characteristics, and referring URLs. 

This information, which includes the pages you visit on our site, which web address you came from, the type of browser/device/hardware you are using, search terms and IP-based geographic location, helps us recognize you, customize your website experience and make our marketing messages more relevant. 

This information is collected and stored using a variety of common technologies, including but not limited to various types of cookies, web beacons, and tags. Our website is not designed to respond to "do not track" requests from browsers. These technologies may also allow us to identify you as a particular Badcock retail store customer when you visit our website, and to link your activities on our website to your interactions with us in our stores. 

To help us understand and enhance our interactions with you, we may permit web analytics and other providers to collect and process information on our website using the technologies described above. We also may share personal information with those providers. 

**Location Information**

Our website may collect certain information such as the type of mobile device you're using or your specific location to help you search for one of our stores. To allow any application to identify your location, you must enable this functionality through your mobile device's settings to allow the use of technologies such as Wi-Fi, GPS signals, cell tower position, or other technologies. Badcock has no control over your device's settings. 

How We Use the Information We Collect

Examples of how we use the information we collect include:

**Product and Service Fulfillment**

  * Fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, returns/exchanges, or requests for information about our products and services in our stores, website, or mobile website, or to otherwise serve you 
  * Connect with Badcock on social media platforms
  * Provide services such as a shopping list
  * Administer sweepstakes and contests

**Our Marketing Purposes**

  * Deliver coupons, mobile coupons, newsletters, in-store receipt messages, e-mails, mobile messages, and social media notifications 
  * Provide interactive features of the website or mobile applications, such as product reviews or marketing communications and other information regarding products, services and promotions 
  * Administer promotions, surveys, and focus groups

**Internal Operations**

  * Improve the effectiveness of our website, stores, mobile experience, and marketing efforts 
  * Conduct research and analysis, including focus groups and surveys 
  * Perform other business activities as needed, or as described elsewhere in this policy 
  * Establishing and managing your accounts with us
  * Communicating things like special events, sweepstakes, promotions and surveys 
  * Processing Badcock credit applications
  * Identifying you on our website and tailoring advertisements and offers to you (both on our website and on other websites) based on your interactions with us in our stores and online 
  * Facilitating interactions with Badcock and others, such as enabling you to e-mail a link to a friend 
  * Operating, evaluating and improving our business

**Fraud Prevention**

  * To prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft and otherwise protect our guests and our business (e.g. product recalls) 

**Fraud Prevention**

For example, assist law enforcement and respond to legal/regulatory inquiries. 

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

How We Share the Information We Collect

**Service Providers**

We may share the information we collect with companies that provide support services to us (such as a printer, e-mail, marketing communications, mobile marketing, research analytics providers, web hosting providers, call center service providers, sweepstakes vendors, credit providers, payment processors, coupon delivery vendors, data enhancement, or fraud prevention providers) or that help us market our products and services. These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions. These companies are not authorized to use the information we share with them for any other purpose. 

**Elsewhere at Your Direction**

At your direction or request, we may share your information. For example, if you create a gift registry or shopping list and elect to make it available to the public, your information will be accessible on our website, mobile or social applications, and on kiosks in our stores. 

**Business Transfers**

We may share personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution or similar event. We also may retain a copy of the information. 

We may share personal information in connection with financial products or services related to our business such as private label credit cards. We may also share personal information in connection with co-branded product or service offerings. For example, if you apply for a Badcock credit card, we may share your personal information with our banking partners that issue the card. 

How We Protect the Information We Collect

**Security Methods**

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect your personal information. When we collect or transmit sensitive information such as a credit or debit card number, we use industry standard methods to protect that information. However, no e-commerce solution, website, database or system is completely secure or "hacker proof." You are also responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse. 

**E-mail Security**

"Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an e-mail that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through e-mail. 

**Badcock Cookies**

The help function of your browser should contain instructions to set your computer to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie is issued, or to not receive cookies at any time. If you set your computer to not receive cookies at any time, certain personalized services cannot be provided to you, and accordingly, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the Badcock.com features. 

Your Choices Regarding the Information We Collect

You may choose to:

  * Stop receiving marketing or promotional e-mails, direct mail, phone and mobile marketing communications 
  * Update and correct your personal information
  * Request that we no longer use your information to provide you services 

**Postal Mail**

If you do not wish to receive catalogs, coupons, and other promotional mail, contact us or call 800-223-2625 to opt out. 

**Telephone**

If you do not wish to receive promotional telephone calls, contact us or call 800-223-2625 to opt out. This opt out does not apply to operational phone calls, for example, confirmation of delivery address. 

**E-mail**

If you do not wish to receive promotional telephone calls, contact us or call 800-223-2625 to opt out. This opt out does not apply to operational phone calls, for example, confirmation of delivery address. 

**Mobile**

We may distribute mobile coupons and text messages to mobile devices of customers who have requested this information via an opt in request. Specific opt out instruction will be contained in each text message. 

To do any of the above, you may also let us know by sending a letter with your request and current contact information to: 

W.S. Badcock Corporation P.O. Box 497 Attention: Marketing Department Mulberry, FL 33860 

**Protecting Children's Privacy**

We are committed to protecting children's privacy on the Internet and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. 

**Links to Other Website**

Our website may link to other websites, many of which have their own privacy policies. Be sure to review the privacy policy on the site you're visiting. 

**Social Media Widgets**

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, Pinterest, and Twitter (and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site). These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**Privacy Policy Updates**

We may need to update our Privacy Policy as Badcock and our customers grow and evolve or to comply with law. If we make material changes, including any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective, as well as inform you of any choices you may have with respect to these changes. 

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or practices, we'll do our best to answer them. Here's how to contact us: 

**Phone:**

1-800-BADCOCK (1-800-223-2625)

**E-mail:**

**Address**

W.S. Badcock Corporation   
P.O. Box 497   
Attention: Marketing Department   
Mulberry, FL 33860 

How Do You Access and Update Your Personal Information?

In order to keep your personal information accurate and complete, you can access or update some of it in the following ways: 

If you have created a Badcock.com account, you can log in and update your account information, including contact, billing, and shipping information. 

Contact us with your current contact information and the personal information you would like to access. We will provide you the personal information requested if reasonably available, or will describe the types of personal information we typically collect. 

**Privacy Policy Scope**

This privacy policy applies to all current or former guest personal information.
